reportedphonenumber.com 2017-06-26

# Privacy - Reported Call Number

Please carefully review the following basic rules that govern your use of the Website. Please note that your use of the Website constitutes your unconditional agreement to follow and be bound by these Terms and Conditions of Use. If you (the "User") do not agree to them, do not use the Website, provide any materials to the Website or download any materials from them.

Information Collected This privacy policy applies only to information collected on the Sites and does not apply to information collected by Discovery through any other means. We collect two types of information from visitors to the Sites: (1) Personally Identifiable Information; and (2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information, such as your IP address or cookies.  

These Terms and Conditions of Use apply to the use of the Website and do not extend to any linked third party sites. These Terms and Conditions and our Privacy Policy, which are hereby incorporated by reference, contain the entire agreement (the “Agreement”) between you and reportedcallnumber.com with respect to the Website. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.  
Permitted and Prohibited Uses

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of having your information included in this directory. You can do this at any time by sending us email or get in touch with us via our contact form and requested your information be removed.

**Cookies and web beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on reportedcallnumber.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).  

**Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

You may use the the Website for the sole purpose of sharing and exchanging ideas/information with other Users. You may not use the the Website to violate any applicable local, state, national, or international law, including without limitation any applicable laws relating to antitrust or other illegal trade or business practices, federal and state securities laws, regulations promulgated by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, any rules of any national or other securities exchange, and any U.S. laws, rules, and regulations governing the export and re-export of commodities or technical data.

You may not upload or transmit any material that infringes or misappropriates any person's copyright, patent, trademark, or trade secret, or disclose via the the Website any information the disclosure of which would constitute a violation of any confidentiality obligations you may have.

You may not upload any viruses, worms, Trojan horses, or other forms of harmful computer code, nor subject the Website's network or servers to unreasonable traffic loads, or otherwise engage in conduct deemed disruptive to the ordinary operation of the Website.

**Third party websites**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Your consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our privacy policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page
